So I come back to Coppilot's homepage and now let's say that I want to ask it for advice on
that very same topic so I want to learn French, right? So hey Coppilot, I'm just getting started
with French. I know English but don't know any French. I want you to start teaching me with
simple helpful phrases, right? So this is my command. I also open this up and okay I don't want to
create a podcast. I don't want deep research. I want to learn. So where was it possible?
It seems like it doesn't have a learning option over here on Coppilot, right? But whatever
create image. Okay, yes start teaching me. I just send my command and then come through, try
uploading again. I didn't have a file. Yes so as you see I get perfect Nima, let's start with
some super practical French phrases that you can use right away. Bonjour, Bonjour, salu,
mercy, silver player, silver player, you know, and these are all that we got. Quick tip,
French pronunciation can feel tricky at first. For example Bonjour, mercy, right? So yep,